<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Martin Lee&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.martinlee.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Martin Lee&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Martin Lee 2017</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 18:56:42 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.martinlee.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How Its Made Pt2 or Hugo in S3 and CloudFront</title>
      <link>https://blog.martinlee.org/posts/how-its-made-pt2-or-hugo-in-s3-and-cloudfront/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 18:56:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.martinlee.org/posts/how-its-made-pt2-or-hugo-in-s3-and-cloudfront/</guid>
      <description>Intro In Part 1 I built my architecture using Route53, S3 and CloudFront. This would suit pretty much any static site, but I chose to use Hugo. Why? I hadn&amp;rsquo;t used it before&amp;hellip;
Bringing it all together Go back and read the first part for how to get yourself a place where you can put static HTML in S3, and then serve it over a CDN with HTTPS through CloudFront - all without using the GUI!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFS for Rancher in Google Cloud Platform</title>
      <link>https://blog.martinlee.org/posts/rancher-gcp-nfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 18:14:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.martinlee.org/posts/rancher-gcp-nfs/</guid>
      <description>Intro Recently, I deployed some Rancher hosts in Google Cloud Platform, taking advantage of some free credit.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been spoiled by Rancher&amp;rsquo;s integration with Amazon Web Services EFS and EBS - making storage for containers very simple. GCP doesn&amp;rsquo;t yet have a similar integration so I had to find another way.
File Servers on Google Compute Engine Google offer some possible solutions in their documentation. I chose to go with the Single Node File Server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Its Made Pt1</title>
      <link>https://blog.martinlee.org/posts/how-its-made-pt1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.martinlee.org/posts/how-its-made-pt1/</guid>
      <description>Intro First thing first, we&amp;rsquo;re going to need some infrastructure to host the blog. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to over-engineer this because I enjoy that sort of thing. I&amp;rsquo;m going to host it entirely in AWS, and as a static site (think Hugo, Jekyll, etc.) By the time your reading this - I&amp;rsquo;ll have made a decision on what to use, but this post was drafted while I was still deciding.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>